wwe.com 2017-12-28

# Privacy Policy | WWE

**World Wrestling Entertainment, Inc. Privacy Policy**  
 **Updated December 1** **, 2017**  

### **Introduction**

The websites <http://network.wwe.com/>, <https://shop.wwe.com/>, <https://euroshop.wwe.com/>, <http://auction.wwe.com/>, <http://www.tapout.com/>, <https://shopexpress.wwe.com/>, [www.wwe.com](http://www.wwe.com/ "www.wwe.com"), [www.WWEToughEnough.com](https://www.wwetoughenough.com/), [http://corporate.wwe.com](http://corporate.wwe.com/) and our WWE Mobile Application (collectively, the “Services”) you have entered are owned and operated by, or on behalf of, World Wrestling Entertainment, Inc. or its affiliates (collectively, "WWE", "we" or "us"). This Privacy Policy applies to the Services unless we have posted a special Privacy Policy to a particular website, in which case the special Privacy Policy terms apply to that website or service to the extent that they are different from this Privacy Policy.

Please note that this Privacy Policy contains capitalized words or phrases. These words and phrases are defined terms. Their definitions are found either in this Privacy Policy or in our [Terms and Conditions of Use](http://www.wwe.com/main-help/generalfaq/terms-and-conditions-wwe "Terms and Conditions of Use") ("Terms of Use"). To help you use this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use, we have made some words, phrases and headings into hyperlinks. These words, phrases and headings have color highlighting.

The WWE’s privacy practices, described in this Privacy Policy, comply with the APEC Cross Border Privacy Rules System.  The APEC CBPR system provides a framework for organizations to ensure protection of personal information transferred among participating APEC economies.  More information about the APEC framework can be [found here](http://www.apec.org/Groups/Committee-on-Trade-and-Investment/~/media/Files/Groups/ECSG/CBPR/CBPR-PoliciesRulesGuidelines.ashx).

If you have a privacy or data use concern that we have not addressed satisfactorily in this Privacy Policy, please contact us at [privacy@wwe.com](mailto:privacy@wwe.com).  If you have an unresolved privacy or data use concern that we have not addressed satisfactorily, please contact our U.S.-based third party dispute resolution provider (free of charge) at <https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request>.

WWE wants to help you make the most of your use of our Services, and that includes helping to protect your personal privacy. Most of the features on our Services are offered without collecting any Personal Information (defined below) from you; however, some features require you to provide your Personal Information. For example, when you make a purchase or sign up for a paid service (such as in the WWE Shop), you are required to submit Personal Information in connection with our providing various products and services to you. You may also submit content of your own in areas of our Services, and some of that User-Generated Content may contain Personal Information. For those aspects of our Services that do require us to collect Personal Information or allow voluntary submission of Personal Information, this Privacy Policy will offer suggestions on how to make good decisions for yourself and your family.

This Privacy Policy discloses when and how we collect, use, share, and safeguard information from our Services. The Personal Information we collect depends on what you do when you visit our websites or use the various products or services we offer. This Privacy Policy also explains what to do if you do not want to provide Personal Information when you use our Services, and how to correct, change or delete some information you have already provided to us.

By using these Services, you are agreeing to the terms of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with any terms or practices described in this Privacy Policy, please do not use our Services or provide your Personal Information to us.

As used in this Privacy Policy, "Personal Information" means any information by which a particular natural person is reasonably identifiable.  

Personal Information includes, for example, a first name or initial and last name; a home or other physical address; a date of birth; an e-mail address or other online contact information; or a telephone number. When Personal Information is collected, you will often know because you will be providing it to us; for example, you may fill out a form on the website or submit information via your account or profile, or in connection with requesting various products or services. When you make a purchase or sign up for a paid service, we will also collect additional Personal Information such as your credit or debit card information or information concerning any other payment mechanism we accept (“Payment Information”). We will use your Personal Information (including your Payment Information) as described in this Privacy Policy and will use your Payment Information to process and complete the transactions you have requested.

### **Children**

WWE is committed to providing special protection for the privacy of children who may visit our Services. We encourage parents to spend time online with their children, become familiar with the features of our Services and participate in the activities offered on our Services. For more information on getting involved in your children's online activities, please go to our [WWE Parents site](https://community.wwe.com/diversity/take-action/parents "WWE Parents"). Our protections for the privacy of children include the following:

We do not knowingly solicit, collect, use or retain any Personal Information, for any purpose whatsoever (including internal or external marketing or promotional purposes), from visitors to these Services who are under the age of 13. In addition, we will delete any records of such Personal Information that come to our attention.

We do not allow visitors who we know are under the age of 13 to be listed in any directory of registered users, to participate in any of our chat services, to register for contests, sweepstakes, promotions, or newsletters, or to receive direct marketing from WWE or from our third-party affiliates or service or product providers.

We do collect Personal Information as part of registration processes so that users can obtain certain services, such as newsletters, and so that they can set up accounts or profiles. WWE’s Terms of Use expressly prohibit persons under the age of 13 from opening such accounts or profiles. We do not knowingly allow children to register and our Services may employ features and procedures that are intended to help prevent under-age registrations. If we believe that a person who is under the age of 13 has registered with us or set up a profile, account, or has otherwise provided information to us without our knowing the person was a child, we may terminate that registration and undertake commercially reasonable efforts to delete any Personal Information we have obtained, including all content from any profile or account.

We recommend that minors who are age 13 or older consult with their parents before sending any information about themselves over the internet.

If we believe a person is under the age of 18, we also retain the right to refuse to process or delete their Personal Information and any Personal Information which they might provide in respect of anyone else, or to stop them from participating in any related features or services, unless they are able to prove to our reasonable satisfaction that they are over the age of 18 or have any (if any) appropriate parental consent to provide Personal Information to us.

### **Special Note to Parents**

If you become aware that your child has provided us with Personal Information at one of our Services, we invite you to notify us so that we may delete the information from our records and discontinue any related features or services (see "Opt-Out" below). We appreciate your cooperation in assisting us to provide a safe and enjoyable online experience for your children.

### **Social Media Features**

Our Services include Social Media Features, such as the Facebook Like button. These Features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our site. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.

### **Facebook Connect or other OpenID provider**

You can log in to our site using sign-in services such as Facebook Connect or an OpenID provider. These services will authenticate your identity and provide you the option to share certain Personal Information with us such as your name and e-mail address to pre-populate our sign-up form. Services like Facebook Connect give you the option to post information about your activities on our Services to your profile page to share with others within your network.   

### **Collection of Personal Information**

WWE collects Personal Information from users of our Services in a number of ways. These may include the following:

  * Subscriptions to our free newsletters, which include updates, special offers and promotions from WWE's various entities, subsidiaries, and affiliates.
  * Participation in contests and sweepstakes.
  * Registrations to receive free downloadable desktop applications (e.g., screensavers).
  * Registrations to send electronic greeting cards.
  * Registrations for individual accounts or profiles.
  * Purchases of merchandise, WWE Network subscriptions, and any other products or services currently offered.
  * E-mail transmitted via various links on our Services.
  * Use of the Services, such as links clicked and items placed in your shopping cart.
  * Registrations for Single Sign-On or other accounts.

The use of any of these services is entirely optional and voluntary; however, if you do not provide the Personal Information requested, you might not be able to register or we may elect to not make the related services available for your use. If you send us an e-mail in which you disclose Personal Information, we will use it to discuss the subject of your correspondence and, if appropriate, share it with other interested parties (such as manufacturers of merchandise you have purchased from a website).

In each case where you submit Personal Information to us via one of our Services, you will be transmitting your Personal Information for processing in the United States of America, where World Wrestling Entertainment, Inc. is headquartered.  Your Personal Information may also need to be transferred, and processed, in other locations outside of your home country.  For more information on this, please see the section below entitled: **Worldwide Transfers and Processing of Personal Information**

If you send us an e-mail, you should know that e-mail is not necessarily secure against interception. So, if your communication needs to include sensitive information like your Payment Information or social security number, please contact us by postal mail or telephone (see "Contact Us" below) rather than e-mail.

We collect your location-based information for the purpose of detecting your location so that we may serve you the correct version of the application, (for instance country, state, city and/or zip code) and display targeted advertising and relevant data to you. Examples of ways in which we use your location-based information include, without limitation, to verify that you are in in a region that is allowed to view WWE Network content, display what events are near you, serve relevant advertising to you, target push notifications/alerts and determine what is shown in the main navigation. We do not use location services to collect any data.

We will only share this information with our mapping provider for the sole purpose of providing you the Services. If you no longer wish to allow us to track your location-based information in the Mobile App you may turn this off at the device level. If you no longer wish to have location-based information collected for the purpose of serving you targeted ads, you may opt-out by clicking [here](http://preferences-mgr.truste.com/). If you are in the EU, please click [here](http://youronlinechoices.eu/). Please note this does not opt you out of being served advertising. You will continue to receive generic ads.

We may provide you the opportunity to participate in contests on our Services. If you participate, we will request certain Personal Information from you. Participation in these contests is completely voluntary and you therefore have a choice whether or not to disclose this information. The requested information typically includes contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as city, state, zip code). We also use this information to notify contest winners and award prizes.

We may also request a video submission containing your physical likeness, height, weight and other Personal Information you voluntarily disclose in the video. We may display user-created video submissions, the user's name, self-identified "nickname" and location (city, state and country) on our Services. Such submissions may be posted to the website and will be visible to other users and visitors of the Services.

### **Tracking** **Technologies**

Technologies such as: cookies, beacons, tags, scripts, and similar technologies are used by WWE, our affiliates and advertising partners and our partners who serve content on our Services. For more information about the Tracking Technologies we use read our [Cookie Policy](http://www.wwe.com/help/generalfaq/data-preferences).  To manage Flash cookies, please click [here](http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager07.html).

We do not respond to browser do-not-track signals at this time.

### **Log Files**

As is true of most websites, we gather certain information automatically through our Services and store such information in log files. This information may include internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and/or clickstream data. We do not link this automatically collected data to other information we collect about you.

### **Push Notifications**

We send you push notifications from time-to-time in order to update you about any events or promotions that we may be running. If you no longer wish to receive these types of communications, you may turn them off at the device level. To ensure you receive proper notifications, we will need to collect certain information about your device such as operating system and user identification information. 

### **Worldwide Transfers and Processing of Personal Information** **and Consent**

All Personal Information that WWE collects through the Services is transferred to, and accessed from, jurisdictions, including the United States where World Wrestling Entertainment, Inc. has its international headquarters.

**Your Consent Declaration**

**By** **accepting this Privacy Policy** **, you consent to having your** **Personal Information** **transferred to, and accessed from, any location worldwide, including the United States** **for the purpose of providing the Services of WWE** **. You also consent to having your Personal Information processed and maintained in any location worldwide, including the United States** **for these purposes.** **You acknowledge that other jurisdictions may have laws that are different than the laws of your home country.**

For visitors to our Services who are based within the European Union, this will involve the processing of your Personal Information outside of the European Economic Area, (the “EEA”). If you do not wish your Personal Information to leave the European Economic Area, or your home country, please do not provide your Personal Information via the Services. If you have already provided your Personal Information, and you require us to stop processing your Personal Information, please contact us at [privacy@wwe.com](mailto:privacy@wwe.com). If you provide your information you are aware that certain governmental authorities may have access to your Personal Information stored in the United States in accordance with your consent. The legal protections and other rights available to those affected in the event of such access by governmental authorities may be different compared to the protection provided in the EEA countries and may not entirely reflect standards imposed under European law. This includes the fact that governmental authorities may request access to your Personal Information without allowing WWE to inform you of such access, and that such requests for (and grants of) access may not be subject to equal limitations with regard to necessity and purpose as would be in effect under European law.  Furthermore, governmental authorities may subject your Personal Information to further processing and such further processing may not be subject to equal limitations with regard to necessity and purpose as would be in effect under European law. Finally, you are aware that governmental authorities in the United States may not be subject to the same types or degree of public control by other authorities or courts as present under European law. 

### **How We Use Your Information**

We limit the manner in which your Personal and Payment Information is used. We will use the Personal and Payment Information you provide only in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Policy. If we obtain Personal or Payment Information from a third party, such as a business partner, our use of that information is also governed by this Privacy Policy. We use Personal and Payment Information for purposes such as: providing you the products and services you want; administering or enforcing transactions you have requested; protecting your accounts from fraud, unauthorized access, or identity theft; verifying your identity in connection with transactions you have requested; managing our business and protecting our interests; and as set out in our [Terms of Use](http://www.wwe.com/main-help/generalfaq/terms-and-conditions-wwe). We may also use Personal Information (but not Payment Information) to allow users of the Services to use a single set of credentials to access the Services, better understand and serve the needs of the WWE community, and to provide news and information to you and community members on new content, products, services, and features of WWE and/or our Services including, without limitation, via direct e-mail. We may use the Personal Information and other information we collect from you to send you marketing emails and other offers we believe may interest you.  For example, if you leave our Site without purchasing items that you have placed in your shopping cart, we may send you an email reminding you about your saved items. Where permitted by (and in compliance with) laws of your jurisdiction (including laws requiring your consent to third party marketing uses of your Personal information), we may also permit select third parties to provide you with information about goods or services which we feel may interest you, via direct e-mail or otherwise.  If you do not want to be contacted in the future by WWE or our advertising partners, please indicate this by not ticking the relevant boxes presented to you on the relevant registration page or otherwise contact us at [privacy@wwe.com](mailto:privacy@wwe.com). For more information, please see the section entitled Managing Your Preferences" below.

We may share Personal and Payment Information with our service providers to assist us with any of the purposes set forth above (which, for example, might include disclosures to attorneys, accountants, auditors, credit bureaus, data processors, payment processors, and technical systems consultants) to the extent necessary or appropriate for them to perform their services to us. In that connection, we may report information about your account(s) to credit bureaus and/or consumer reporting agencies. By way of example, if you order a product or service from us or register for one of our contests, promotions, or interactive services, WWE may share Personal Information with other service providers, suppliers and other third parties (for example, sweepstakes sponsors or delivery services) that assist us in operating the websites or providing the products or services.

We may share Personal and Payment Information in the event that (i) we sell or buy any business or assets, in which case we may disclose your personal data to the prospective seller or buyer of such business or assets, or (ii) if WWE or substantially all of its assets are acquired by a third party, in which case personal data held by it about its customers will be one of the transferred assets.

We do not share your Personal Information to third parties except as described in this Privacy Policy or as permitted under applicable law.

Please note that we will release your Personal or Payment Information if required to do so by law, search warrant, subpoena, court order or other legal process. WWE may also disclose your Personal or Payment Information if we have a good faith belief that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to detect or prevent fraud or to protect the rights, property, health or personal safety of WWE, WWE employees, our third party licensors, customers or the public. We may also disclose your Personal or Payment Information if you or your legal representative authorizes us to do so, or if it is necessary to perform credit checks or collect or report debts owed to us. 

### **Links to Third Party Websites/Mobile Applications**

Our Services contain or may contain certain hyperlinks to other third party websites or mobile applications, some of which may display WWE's logos or other WWE content. These websites and mobile applications may have privacy policies; however, all of these websites, mobile applications and their privacy policies are independent of our websites or this Privacy Policy. WWE is not responsible for compliance with other websites' or mobile applications' privacy policies or data collection practices. You should review these privacy policies carefully before providing any Personal Information to these websites or mobile applications.

### **Third Party Ad Servers and Advertisements**

Ads appearing on our websites may be delivered to you by DoubleClick, or by other third party advertising companies.  Information about your visits to our websites and third party websites, such as number of times you have viewed an ad, date/time at which the ads were shown, the advertisers' cookies (browser or Flash) or other technologies, and the IP address of the computer you use is used to serve ads to you on our websites. We do not have access to the cookies that may be placed by our third party advertising companies. We share website usage information about visitors to our websites with these companies for our purposes, and for their purposes, which include – for example – managing and targeting advertisements, measuring their effectiveness, and for market research analysis. For these purposes, we and third-party advertising companies we use may note the pages you visit on our sites. For more information about DoubleClick, please see <http://www.google.com/doubleclick/> and <http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/>.

### **Limitations on Use of Personal Information**

We will use or retain your Personal Information only in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy or as allowed by applicable law. In general, we strive to keep Personal Information only for so long as is needed to fulfill your requests, support Single Sign-On and the services you have requested, process your orders, or comply with the law, although we reserve the right to keep it for a longer period of time, if necessary.

### **Security of Personal Information**

We take what we believe to be appropriate physical, administrative and technical precautions in an effort to create security for your Personal Information, including the use of Transport Layer Security technology to help protect the transmission of Payment Information.

### **Managing Your Preferences**

In general, features on our websites requiring registration allows you to either opt-in or opt-out from receiving updates, special offers, promotions, marketing or other correspondence from either us or our business affiliates or advertising partners. You can reverse your decision any time by following the unsubscribe instructions contained in the e-mail communications you receive. Alternatively, please contact us at [privacy@wwe.com](mailto:privacy@wwe.com) with your request. In each case please be sure to include your name and e-mail address in the e-mail, and all other relevant information, so that we can properly action your request and remove that information from our list.

We partner with a third party ad network to either display advertising on our websites and mobile application or to manage our advertising on other sites. To learn more, please read our [Cookie Policy](http://www.wwe.com/help/generalfaq/data-preferences).

### **Access/Correct/Update/Delete Personal Information**

If you would like to know what Personal Information WWE has concerning you, send an e-mail to [privacy@wwe.com](mailto:privacy@wwe.com). We will be in contact with you (by mail or otherwise) to verify your identity and provide you the information you request. We will respond within 30 days to your request for access to your Personal Information. In some cases, we may not be able to remove your Personal Information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why. Even if we are able to make your content no longer visible, this does not ensure complete or comprehensive removal of your content or personal information from the Internet as third parties may retain screen shots and/or share your video on other websites.

If you would like to correct or update your Personal Information, click [here](http://www.wwe.com/my-profile) and sign into your account. If you would like to delete your account or remove your information from our blog or community forum, send an e-mail to [privacy@wwe.com](mailto:privacy@wwe.com).

However, any information that has been posted as a comment or blog, gallery, or forum entry cannot be deleted by users and may be seen by others. WWE reserves the right to delete any User-Generated Content that it determines is no longer of relevance to the community, to free up memory or for any other reason in its discretion.

### **Changes** **to** **this Privacy Policy**

WWE reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time. If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes here and we will change the "Updated" date at the top of this page. If we make any material changes we will notify you by e-mail (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a prominent notice on this site prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to visit this area frequently to stay informed.

### **Contact Us**

If you have any comments or questions about this Privacy Policy, please send an e-mail to [privacy@wwe.com](mailto:privacy@wwe.com).

You may also contact at us by postal mail or telephone at:

WWE Member Services  
1241 East Main Street  
Stamford, CT 06902  
(203) 352-8600
